-  Michelle: What are you making for breakfast dad?
- Danny: Something to go kids, we’re running late
- Michelle: But I want Belgian waffles, apple smoked bacon and sourdough toast, lightly buttered.
* laughter *
- Stephanie: Yeah, and I want straight A's, world peace and Brad Pitt  * mockingly * lightly buttered.
- Danny: No buttered bread and definitely no buttered Brad * laughter *
- Danny: If you've got time for anything you can stick your finger through
- Danny: *sticks bread through their index fingers* Ladies. *laughter*
- Michelle: Tomorrow I'm gonna get up early and cook my own breakfast
- * laughter *
- Michelle: Wait a minute...I don't even know how to cook *laughter*
- Becky: Well Michelle, I'll teach you how to cook
- Jessie: Well that's sweet honey...but, who's gonna teach you?
- * laughter *
- Becky: Come on stop teasing me, I'm a good cook!
- Becky: Remember that sausage and lima bean casserole I made?
- I called it my Sunday Surprise
- Danny: We called it our Monday surprise
* laughter *
- Jessie: I was still getting surprised on Tuesday
- Becky: Yeah well I bet you won't be getting surprised tonight
- Jessie: Oh! Woah! Check Please * laughter *
- Becky: Michelle, what do you say?
- You and me after school, making dinner.
- Michelle: I'm there.